http://www.remix64.com/privacy-notice.html

search
VOTING DEADLINE FOR REMIXER OF THE YEAR AWARDS: 45 days left
Privacy notice Remix64 is a private, non-profit hobby project. Your data owner rights You can always exercise the following rights by contacting us:
Information about your stored data and their processing, Correction of incorrect personal data, Deletion of your stored data, Restriction of data processing, if we are not yet allowed to delete your data due to legal obligations, Objection to the processing of your data by us and Data portability, if you have consented to the data processing or have concluded a contract with us.
If you have given us your consent, you can revoke it at any time with effect for the future. You can always contact the supervisory authority responsible for you with a complaint. Your competent supervisory authority will depend on the state of your domicile, work or alleged violation. A list of the supervisory authorities (for the non-public area) with address can be found at: www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html. Purposes of data processing by the responsible body and third parties We process your personal data only for the purposes stated in this privacy policy. A transfer of your personal data to third parties for purposes other than those mentioned does not take place. We only share your personal information with third parties if:
You have given your express consent to the processing is required to execute a contract with you, the processing is necessary to fulfill a legal obligation,
processing is necessary to protect legitimate interests and there is no reason to believe that you have an overriding legitimate interest in not disclosing your information. Deletion or blocking of data We adhere to the principles of data avoidance and data economy. Therefore, we only store your personal data for as long as is necessary to achieve the purposes mentioned here or as provided for by the various storage periods provided for by law. After discontinuation of the respective purpose or expiration of these deadlines, the corresponding data will be routinely and in accordance with the statutory provisions blocked or deleted. Collecting general information when visiting our website When you access our website, our provider's server log file automatically records information of general nature. This information includes, for example, the type of web browser, the operating system used, the domain name of your Internet service provider and the like. This information does not allow conclusions about your person. This information is necessary to correctly deliver the contents of web pages requested by you and is mandatory when using the internet. They are processed in particular for the following purposes:
Ensuring a hassle-free connection of the website, Ensuring a smooth use of our website, Evaluation of system security and stability as well for further administrative purposes.
The processing of your personal data is based on our legitimate interest for the aforementioned purposes of data collection. We do not use your information to draw conclusions about you. The recipient of the data is only the responsible body and possibly the processor. Anonymous information of this kind may be statistically evaluated by us to optimize our website and the underlying technology. Cookies Our website always sets a Session-Cookie. This cookie stores the server's session ID on your device. The session is started to optimize the website output, tailored to fit your device. Under no circumstances, we will disclose this data to third parties, or connect it to your personal data without your consent. You may also chose to view our website without cookies. Internet browsers are regularly set to accept cookies. In general, you can disable the use of cookies at any time through the settings of your browser. Please use the help features of your internet browser to find out how to change these settings. Please note that some features of our website may not work if you have disabled the use of cookies. SSL encryption To protect the security of your data during transmission, we use state-of-the-art encryption techniques (such as SSL) over HTTPS. Posting comments When users leave comments on our site, we will store the posting time and the username chosen by the site visitor. These are means for our protection, as we may be prosecuted for any illegal content on our website, even if created by users.   Contact form By contacting us via e-mail or contact form concerning any matter, you are giving us your consent to use your data for the purpose of establishing contact. This requires the specification of a valid e-mail address. This serves for the assignment of the request and the subsequent answering of the same. The specification of further data is optional. The information you provide will be stored for the purpose of processing the request and for possible follow-up questions. After completing the request, your personal data will be deleted. Social sharing buttons Our Sharing Buttons of the social networks do not use social plugins of the corresponding services (Facebook, Twitter etc), but are merely references to the respective services. This means that these services can not record your surfing behavior on our website via the buttons. If you click on a share button, the affected service will know which page you want to share. Embedded YouTube videos On some of our web pages, we embed Youtube videos. The corresponding plug-ins are operated by YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. When you visit a page with the YouTube plug-in, it will connect to Youtube's servers. Youtube will be informed which pages you visit. If you are logged into your Youtube account, Youtube can assign your surfing behavior to you personally. This can be prevented by logging out of your Youtube account beforehand. If a Youtube video is started, the provider uses cookies that collect information about user behavior. Anyone who has disabled the storage of cookies for the Google Ad program will not have to expect such cookies when watching YouTube videos. Youtube also stores non-personal usage information in other cookies. If you want to prevent this, you must block the storage of cookies in the browser. Further information on data protection on Youtube can be found in the provider's privacy policy at: www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy Subsequent changes to our privacy policy We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy to comply with the latest legal requirements or to implement changes to our privacy policy, such as the introduction of new services. Your latest visit will be subject to the latest privacy policy. Got questions? If you have questions about privacy, please contact us.
The privacy policy was partly created with the Privacy policy generator of activeMind AG, and then translated to english to the best of my abilities.
shareShare
shareShare
keyboard_arrow_up to top
Our website uses cookies, to protect and to improve our services. If you continue to use our website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
keyboard_arrow_right Imprint
keyboard_arrow_right Privacy notice
check I agree.
